## HIDEAKI MYAMURA

## Senior Fullstack Developer

+447470723109 Dreamfullstacker@gmail.com Tokyo, Japan

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

01/2017 - 07/2019

Rikkeisoft Osaka

Rikkeisoft has delivered 1000+ projects, many with big Japanese corporations. Average customer satisfaction rate of Rikkeisoft is 90%, largely due to our thorough quality assurance and testing at every stage and prior to final project delivery.

- Leading a small team on a variety of development projects and delivering solutions to meet and exceed client's briefs
- Responsive design
- Version control systems

#### SENIOR Blockchain DEVELOPER

10/2019 - 12/2021

METHOD IT Tokyo

METHOD IT offers IT services and solutions to companies in Tokyo. METHOD IT do this because we have a passion for the latest business technologies and service with a personal touch.

- Worked alongside the senior web developers to deliver optimum performance of client's websites.
- Build smart contract
- Deploy and test
- Continuous integration

#### **EDUCATION**

High School Diploma 09/2009 - 09/2013

Waseda University Senior High School

Computer Science 10/2013 - 04/2017

Waseda University

### **SUMMARY**

If given a choice, my desired job title would be that of lead senior full stack engineer. My seven years of experience in web, app development plus my education in professional and technical writing make me an ideal candidate for this position and have additionally prepared me to take on more leadership-oriented roles such as full stack engineer

I like to be in the back and front of tech hence my passion for web and blockchain development.

I put my heart and soul into every project I work on, going non-stop till it is brought to perfection.

My strongest attribute is my determination. I take on every challenge head-on and do what I need to accomplish my goals, even when the challenge is difficult My unique attribute is passion. I think without a passion for what you are doing, it is not possible to ideally perform your job.

Just thinking of programming as my hobby, I started my career for software development in the companies when I was studying at the Waseda University. This was an amazing experience for me to grow as an IT technician. I will never give up on my way. Thanks for reading!



### **SKILLS**

Blockchain Cryptocurrency NFT

Solidity Codeigniter Laravel · ·

Node.js· Express MongoDB ·

MySQL React.js Next.js Vue.js

Nuxt.js Vue storefront Angular.js ·

Nest.js·Svelte Bootstrap ·

TailwindCSS GateBy jQuery

Shopify Amazon Web Service ·

React Native Flutter ·

LAMP MERN MEVN MEAN
Working with command lines
Version control systems
DevOps practices
Front-end systems Debugging

### **STRENGTHS**

## Sociability

Client's satisfaction
ACHIEVEMENTS

# I'm graduated Waseda university

A Progressive University Of Traditions
Waseda's culture and tradit

Waseda's culture and traditions have evolved over time since 1882, but its founding principles remain firm. The Waseda spirit lives in the hearts of over 600.000 alumni.

## **LANGUAGES**

Japanese Native
English Proficient

#### **PASSIONS**

NFT Marketplace Platform 2021.8 ~ 2021.10



Stack: Solidity, Binance Smart Chain, NFT, Angular, Typescript, Web3.js, Bootstrap.

Description: Vigallery is NFT marketplace platform and users can connect their wallet to this website and create their NFT. And they can explore all NFTs and can sell or buy NFT they favourite.

2. Extra Matic stacking site 2022.02 ~ 2022.03



Stack: solidity, Polygon chain, React.js, Web3.js, Bootstrap, JS/TS, Truffle.

Description: Extra Matic is Polygon Crypto stacking site. Frontend is built by React.js and smart contract is built by solidity and deployed on Polygon chain. On website, users can deposit some token follow plans. After days, they can withdraw their token based on plan.

3. Panda Coin 2022.05 ~2022.06



Stack: solidity, smart contract, ERC20, React.js, React-bootstrap, JS/TS, web3.js, BlockNative, Moralis API, PancakeSwap API.

Description: Panda Coin is deployed Ethereum main chain and based on ERC20 standard.

Frontend built by React.js and use BlockNative to connect to multi wallet. For token price, use Moralis API and for token swap, use PancakeSwap API.

4. Plata 3B Shopping Site 2020. 12 ~ 2021.03



Stack: React.js, JS/TS, Axios, Express.js, MongoDB.

5. Real Estate Website 2021.04~2021.05



Stack: Angular, JS/TS, Laravel, MySQL

6. Live Video stream Shopping website 2022. 03 ~ 2022. 05

## leeveo

Stack: React.js, Material UI, Typescript, Amazon Web Service(IVS, API Gateway, Lambda, DynamoDB, S3, Amplify, Route53)

7. Movie Stream Website 2019. 11 ~ 2020. 04



Stack: Vue.js TailwindCSS, Laravel, MySQL, Cloudfront.